http://www.jogordon.com/pages/privacy-policy

1. NAME & CONTACT DETAILS OF ORGANISATION
JO GORDON LTD,
7 DRUCE ROAD,
LONDON,
3. PURPOSES OF DATA COLLECTION
Jo Gordon respects your right to privacy and will not collect any personal information on this website without your clear permission. We do not require you to provide personal information for any reason other than to process and deliver an order or to inform you of upcoming Jo Gordon news through our mailing list.
4. LAWFUL BASIS FOR PROCESSING YOUR INFORMATION
We understand that your privacy is important and we will treat any personal information that you provide us with as confidential and this will only be used in accordance with the Data Protection Acts of 1988 and 2003. We will treat as confidential, all of the personal information that you give us when you register using the facility on this website. This includes your name, address, email address, telephone contact numbers and banking details.
5. LEGITIMATE INTEREST FOR PROCESSING YOUR INFORMATION
By choosing to use this website to place an order with us, you agree to our use of your personal information as required to process and deliver your order.
Our website is hosted by Shopify and our mailing list is hosted by Mailchimp. All personal information remains with Shopify and Mailchimp and we do not hold paper copies of personal details in our office. Both these organisations have strict Data Protection Policies and are GDPR compliant.
Jo Gordon Ltd will never share your personal details with a third party (unless obliged or permitted to disclose such information by law).
6. REMOVING YOURSELF FROM OUR MAILING LIST
You have a right at any time to request us to stop sending you marketing information. You can unsubscribe directly and with immediate effect by clicking the link at the bottom of any marketing email we send. Alternatively, you can email us at info@jogordon.com or write to us using the address at the top of the page.
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
choosing a selection results in a full page refresh
